翻譯：沒空來翻賽太公  我幫你翻YY貓  貓中之王  醉芝士
校對：沒空來校賽太公  我幫你校YY貓  總監 YY貓
后期：加森   時間軸：YY貓
生活大爆炸
第七季  第九集
我們用數學算過了
The math is all there.
-這不可能  -的確可能
- It's not real. - Yes, it is.
好吧  聽著
Yeah... uh, look.
從科學角度上來說  單憑一人之力
It is scientifically impossible
不可能從側面將牛推倒
for a person to tip a cow.
Tip a cow over是指在牛站著睡覺的時候悄悄走到旁邊
將其推倒取樂的一種活動
就連你這個虎背熊腰的女漢子
Even you, with your stocky build and lumberjack shoulders,
也不可能做到
you couldn't do it.
太可怕了  你為什么要把牛推到
It's horrible. Why would you push a cow over?
它們多神圣啊
They're sacred.
印度人敬牛如敬神
少來了
Oh, stop it.
我都見你吃過不下一百萬個牛肉漢堡了
I've seen you eat, like, a million hamburgers.
動物可以集神圣和美味于一身
Hey, an animal can be both sacred and delicious.
告訴你們  我的確把牛推倒過
Look, I'm telling you I've done it, okay?
我清楚地記得牛先是站著的
I clearly remember the cow standing up
然后就倒到一側了
and then the cow on its side.
你是不是喝醉了
Were you drunk?
我當時是內布拉斯加州的16歲少女  你覺得呢
I was 16 in Nebraska. What do you think?
我覺得你才是倒下的那個
I think you're the one who fell over.
怪不得當時天空也也倒在一側
That would explain why the sky was also on its side.
霍華德  "推牛倒"是真的還是假的
Howard. Cow tipping: real or not?
我覺得是  假的
I'm gonna say... not.
因為我曾試過在我媽打鼾時讓她翻身
That's just based on me trying to roll my mom over
可死都推不動她
when she's snoring.
說到大塊的肉
Speaking of that big side of beef,
她邀請你們去她家過感恩節
uh, she's invited all of you to Thanksgiving at her house.
有人跟我說  赤裸裸地拒絕別人的邀請
You know, I've been told that a bald refusal
是很無禮的
of an invitation is rude
所以必須編造一個禮貌的借口來回絕
and one must instead offer up a polite excuse, so...
我也很想去  但不幸的是
I'd love to go, but, unfortunately,
那聽起來很可怕
that sounds awful.
去嘛  一點都不可怕
Come on, it'll be fun.
我們其實打算在這里過
Uh, we were actually gonna do it here.
拜托啦  伯納黛特的媽媽不在家
Please? Bernadette's bringing her dad
所以她會帶她爸來
'cause her mom's out of town,
可我跟他爸總是話不投機
and I never have anything to say to that guy.
既然你都這么說了  我也想幫你
Oh, since you put it that way, I'd love to go,
但那聽起來更可怕了
but that sounds even more awful.
其實不用一天都聽
It'd actually be nice to not hear
謝爾頓抱怨我的廚藝挺好的
Sheldon complain about my cooking all day.
什么  不好意思
Yo... uh, excuse me,
但每年你的菜都做得難吃
but every year you prepare a terrible meal
我每年都批評你的廚藝
and every year I criticize it.
難道我們的傳統對你來說毫無意義嗎
Do our traditions mean nothing to you?
-我想去  -我也是
- I want to go. - Yeah, me, too.
-我也去  -謝爾頓
- I'm in. - Sheldon.
好吧  我去
Ugh, fine, I'll go.
但如果菜都很好吃  那感恩節就被毀了
But if her food is delicious, Thanksgiving is ruined,
這筆賬算你的
and it's on you.
我們真的要去沃羅威茨夫人家吃飯嗎
Do we really have to go to Mrs. Wolowitz's house?
是的
We do.
我希望你的行為舉止要得當
And I expect you to be on your best behavior.
現在我了解非洲黑奴當時的感受了
Now I know how the African slaves felt.
被人強行從自己家園拖出
Being dragged from their homes
淪為受白人控制和使喚的勞力
to labor under the yoke of the white man.
你真的要把
Are you honestly comparing
去沃羅威茨媽媽家吃飯
Thanksgiving dinner at Wolowitz's mom's
和人類歷史上最大的悲劇之一
with one of the greatest tragedies
這兩件事相提并論嗎
in the history of mankind?
是的
Yes.
謝爾頓  不管在哪里都可以過個開心的感恩節
Sheldon, you can have a nice Thanksgiving anywhere.
我就在維加斯試過
I spent one in Vegas.
是嗎
You did?
對啊  當時我在跟扎克約會
Yeah, back when I was dating Zack.
那個感恩節比我想象中有趣多了
It was actually more fun than I thought.
我們先去賭博  然后去了一家低檔的婚禮教堂
We gambled, we went to one of those cheesy wedding chapels,
我們還吃了一頓超美味的火雞大餐
we had a really good turkey dinner.
真的想不到這么好吃  因為我們是在脫衣舞俱樂部
Which was surprising, since we were at a strip club.
慢著  你們倆還去教堂了嗎
Wait, you went to a chapel?
-是啊  -去干嘛
- Yeah. - Why?
我們不過是辦了一場假婚禮
We had one of those silly fake weddings.
拉斯維加斯辦理結婚無需繁瑣的手續
只要新郎新娘兩個人說"我愿意"就可以
佩妮
Penny...
你知道那是真結婚  對吧
you know those are real, right?
不  是假結婚
No, they're not.
是真的
Yeah, they are.
是假的
No, they're not.
是真的
Yeah, they are.
-他說得對  -是真的
- He's right. - They're real.
但那看上去不像真的呀
But it... didn't seem real.
我問你個問題
Let me ask you a question.
有沒可能  當時你眼中的拉斯維加斯是倒在一側的呢
At any point, was Las Vegas on its side?
-爸爸  -乖寶貝
- Hi, Dad. - Hi, honey.
你還給大家買了啤酒啊
Oh, you brought beer for everybody.
好吧  沒錯  人人都有份
Uh, okay, yeah, it's for everybody.
我真是只想今天安靜地在家待著
I really just wanted to have a nice, quiet day at home
看看比賽
and watch the game.
你在這里也能安靜待著看比賽啊
You can have a quiet day and watch the game here.
霍華德  那藥不管用
Howard, the medicine's not working!
你剛吃了沒多久
You just took it.
至少等它先到達你第一個胃再說
At least let it reach your first stomach!
邁克  來了啊
Hey, Mike.
-我來幫你拿吧  -謝謝
- Let me help you out, there. - Thanks.
你媽媽怎么了
What's wrong with your mom?
她的痛風加重了
Oh, her gout's flaring up.
看來一天一個蘋果派
Turns out an apple pie a day
并不能讓你遠離疾病
does not keep the doctor away.
為什么我的小腳趾這么疼呢
How can one little toe hurt so bad?
或許是因為那只小腳趾
Maybe because that little piggy
被你的龐大的身軀壓碎了
is being crushed by the barn!
她很快就會安靜下來
She should quiet down soon.
我給她的止痛藥足以讓一頭...
I gave her enough pain meds to choke a...
讓她安靜下來
well, her.
我們得開始做飯了
I guess we're gonna have to do all the cooking.
我有個更好的主意
I have a better idea.
如果你想讓我一個人干所有的活
If you think you're gonna make me do all this by myself,
那絕對不行
you're crazy.
我是想讓拉杰一個人干所有的活
I was gonna make Raj do it all by himself.
那真是個好主意
Oh, well, that's a great idea.
路上沒車  真是一帆風順啊
No traffic, we're sailing.
是啊
Yes.
好像我們在船上一樣
Like we're on a ship.
一艘從非洲到美國的船
Coming from Africa to America.
謝爾頓  這樣做太不恰當了
Sheldon, that's completely inappropriate.
你不能一直將自己比作奴隸
You can't keep comparing yourself to a slave.
是的  艾米小姐
Yes, Miss Amy.
真不敢相信你居然跟那個傻蛋結婚了
I can't believe you're married to that idiot.
別說了行嗎  我們只是鬧著玩的
Ugh, would you stop? We just did it as a goof.
不管是不是鬧著玩  你們都是真結婚了
Well, a goof or not, you're actually married.
-你得解決這件事  -我會的
- You need to get this taken care of. - I will.
你干嘛在這件事上小題大作
Why are you making this such a big deal?
我知道原因
Oh, oh, oh, I have a reason.
可能是因為你愿意嫁給扎克
It could be because you said yes to marrying Zack,
而每次萊納德向你求婚時
but every time Leonard's proposed,
你總是拒絕他
he's gotten a resounding no.
我一下子就想到這個答案了
Yeah, that's just off the top of my head.
那我該怎么辦
So how do I undo this?
我希望你能解除婚約
I'm hoping you can get an annulment.
就好像這事從來沒發生過
It's just like it never happened.
好啊  那我應該怎么做
Great, well, what do I have to do?
從法律上說  解除婚約
It says here you can get an annulment
必須滿足一下任何一個條件
if any of the following conditions are met.
"婚后  兩人從未圓房"
"Were you unable to consummate the marriage?"
佩妮是欲女  下一條
Penny? Next.
"兩人間存在欺騙  重婚
"Is there any evidence of fraud, bigamy,
缺乏諒解"
want of understanding?"
到底什么是"缺乏諒解[理解力]"
"Want of understanding?" What does that even mean?
叮叮叮  說的就是你
Ding, ding, ding. We have a winner.
謝謝你救我于水火之中
Thanks for saving the day.
不用謝
Ah, no problem.
美國的第一個感恩節是印第安人與新移民第一次齊聚感謝上天賜予
并感謝印第安人曾在危急的時刻送來食物和幫助他們
沒有印第安人[印度人]獻上美食
It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
就不算是真正的感恩節
without an Indian providing the food.
你媽媽把植物奶油放哪里了
Uh, now, where does your mom keep the Crisco?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
大概是塞在她臉頰的肥肉里了
Probably in a wad in her cheek.
我在這里幫拉杰
I'll help Raj in here.
你出去陪我爸爸好嗎
Why don't you go keep my dad company?
他可不想我陪他
Oh, he doesn't want me in there.
我在他眼中是  睡了他乖女兒的討厭鬼
I'm the creepy little guy who has sex with his daughter.
-別傻了  他喜歡你  -真的嗎
- Don't be silly, he loves you. - Does he?
-好吧  至少他關心你啊  -真的嗎
- Okay, he cares about you a lot. - Really?
老娘不也經常為你做牛做馬  快滾出去
I do crap for you all the time. Get out there.
你太太和孫子們一起待在亞利桑那嗎
So your wife's in Arizona with the grandkids?
我媽媽也去過亞利桑那州
You know, my mom's been to...Arizona.
她騎著一頭騾子穿越大峽谷
She rode one of those mules down in the Grand Canyon.
最后為了讓騾子落個安樂死  人們把它射死了
Long story short, they had to shoot it.
因為我媽實在太胖了
'Cause she's so fat.
您慢慢笑  我去開門
I'll get the door while you finish laughing.
大家好
Hey, guys.
感恩節快樂
Happy Thanksgiving.
聞起來真香啊
It smells wonderful.
是誰在廚房做苦力
Is anyone slaving away in the kitchen?
-因為我也...  -謝爾頓
- Because I, too, know... - Sheldon.
給你  謝謝你邀請我們
Here. Thank you for having us.
-你怎么了  -她在生我的氣
- What's with you? - Oh, she's mad at me
因為她剛發現她和扎克結婚了
because she just found out she's married to Zack.
真的嗎
Really?
那個和她約會過的傻蛋嗎
That dumb-ass she used to date?
這也太搞笑了
That's hysterical.
虧我還為在車里打開了這酒而自責
I can't believe I felt bad for opening this in the car.
-你倆要幫忙嗎  -好呀
- You need any help? - Uh, yeah,
你能拿一下上面的醬汁碗嗎
can you, uh, reach that, uh, gravy boat up there?
-沒問題  -太好了
- Uh, sure. - Great.
至少你倆還有人能夠得著
That makes one of you.
我們任務重大  時間卻很緊迫
Okay, we have a lot to do and not much time to do it.
伯納黛特  你負責玉米  肉醬汁和紅薯
Bernadette, you're on corn, gravy and yam detail.
艾米  你負責面包卷  蔓越莓
Amy, you're on rolls, cranberries
并且確保不讓伯納黛特靠近棉花糖
and making sure Bernadette stays away from the marshmallows.
沒錯  我看見你偷吃了
That's right, I see you.
如果有問題要問
Okay, if you have any questions,
我就在這里  專心地給烤肉刷油
I'll be over here basting my ass off.
集中注意力是關鍵
Focus is key.
你們知道佩妮和扎克三年前就結婚了嗎
Did you guys know Penny married Zack three years ago?
-什么  -啥
- What? - Wha...?
你打過橄欖球嗎
You ever play football?
大學時玩過一點
A little in college.
-你呢  -沒玩過
- You? - No.
不過我曾經作為球  被人在走廊阻截過一次
But I did get tackled in the hallway once.
整個學校歡聲雷動啊
The whole school cheered.
我找到了你和扎克
Hey, I found the, uh, court papers
需要填寫的法庭文件
that you and Zack need to fill out.
-等我回家就打印出來  -行
- I'll print them when we get home. - Fine.
然后我們就可以徹底忘掉這事了
And we can just put this whole thing behind us.
-你有完沒完  -怎么了
- Are you done? - What?
我知道  我做錯了
Look, I get it, I screwed up.
難道今天剩下的時間  你都要提起這件事嗎
Is this all we're gonna talk about the rest of the day?
你對我兇什么呀
Why are you mad at me?
明明是你做了蠢事
You're the one that did the stupid thing.
而我只是幫你解決而已
I'm just trying to fix it.
我需要呼吸點新鮮空氣
I need some air.
那個...佩妮
Well... Penny.
我雖然完全不了解女人
Now, I don't know the first thing about women,
但我要是你  我就不會跟出去
but I would not follow her.
聽瘦高個的話沒錯
Listen to Stretch.
怎么成了我的錯了
How am I the bad guy?
是她亂嫁人  我是受害者好嗎
She's the one who married someone else. I'm the victim.
扎克才是受害者吧
Sounds like Zack's the victim.
你睡了人家老婆
You're sleeping with his wife.
我的婚姻35年來一直幸福和睦
I've kept my marriage together for 35 years.
我能給點建議嗎
Can I weigh in here?
好呀
Sure.
我正在看比賽呢  閉嘴
I'm trying to watch the game. Shut up.
怎么會錯過第一次進攻呢
How do you not make a first down there?
人家用了五個后衛  他們還敢傳球
They passed against a nickel defense.
應該采取擺脫攔截才對
They should have run it off-tackle.
你怎么會看球
How the hell do you know that?
我爸愛死橄欖球了
My father loved football.
他總是強迫我一起看
He always made me watch it
不看完不準做作業
before I was allowed to do my homework.
你高興了吧  我剛打電話給扎克了
Well, you'll be happy to know I just spoke to Zack
他會簽那些文件的
and he's willing to sign the court papers.
他馬上就過來
He's on his way here now.
-等等  你居然讓他來這  -是呀
- Wait, you invited him here? - Yeah.
我準備再次發表建議了
I'm getting ready to weigh in again.
過來
Come on.
你覺得他們現在應該怎么做
What do you think they ought to do now?
我會快速斜向往球場內出發  扔球給外接手
I would throw a quick slant to a wideout,
因為防守線衛似乎要向傳球員突襲了
given that the defense is showing blitz.
我最喜歡薄餅卷了
Oh, I love a good blitz,
尤其是加酸奶油的那種
especially with sour cream.
懂我笑點嗎
Get it?
因為這兩者音很近啊
'Cause it sounds like "Blintz."
剛有人說"薄餅卷"嗎
Did someone say "Blintz"?!
我不明白你為什么非得今天把他叫來
I just don't understand why you invited him here today.
因為你嘮叨個沒完
Because you wouldn't shut up about it.
我打給他時  他反正也沒事干
When I called him, he had nothing to do,
所以我就想...
so I just thought it would...
兩位  我在里面做飯呢
Hey, guys, I'm trying to cook in here.
抱歉  我們會小點聲的
Oh, sorry. We'll keep it down.
不  大聲點
No, no, speak up.
我要用攪拌器了
I'm about to use the blender,
可我一句也不想漏掉
and I don't want to miss anything.
你要多準備一人份的食物了
Well, you might have to cook for one more
因為她邀請了扎克過來
because she invited Zack.
-什么  -哇哦
- What? - Ooh!
我的天
My, my.
故事發展如同我的肉汁  越加復雜[濃厚]了
The plot, like my gravy, thickens.
我不喜歡你媽的衛生間
I don't care for your mother's bathroom.
不管你面朝哪邊尿尿
There's not an angle to do one's business
都有一個小丑雕像瞪著你
without a clown figurine staring at you.
所以我才坐著尿
That's why I sit.
沒錯  所以你才不爺們
Yeah, that's why.
你還記得達拉斯下大雪的
You remember the Thanksgiving game
那次感恩節比賽嗎
when it snowed in Dallas?
1993年
1993--
里昂·萊特在最后幾秒犯了錯
Leon Lett blew the game in the final seconds
海豚隊取得了勝利
and the Dolphins emerged victorious.
于是我終于能做我的微積分題了
Then I finally got to do my calculus.
我當時氣瘋了  差點沒一槍崩了電視
I was so pissed, I wanted to shoot my TV.
我爸也是
So was my dad.
他真的開了槍
And then he did.
-有人還要啤酒嗎  -我要
- Anyone need a beer?-  Yeah.
謝天謝地
Thank God.
你爸爸還住在德克薩斯嗎
So, does your dad still live in Texas?
不  我十四歲時他就死了
No. He died when I was 14.
真是太遺憾了
I'm sorry to hear that.
本地酒店的老板也很遺憾
So was the man who owned the local liquor store.
他泣不成聲  痛哭流涕
He cried and cried.
啤酒來了
Here you go.
謝謝
Oh, thanks.
既然你爸在你十四歲就過世了
So, if your dad died when you were 14,
你肯定沒機會和他一起喝啤酒吧
you were never old enough to have a beer with the man.
是的  先生
No, sir.
我高中畢業時他想跟我喝一罐
He did try to give me one for my high school graduation,
但我才11歲  我媽媽說不行
but I was 11 and my mom said no.
那你就跟我喝一罐吧
Well, you're having one with me.
好的
All right.
敬你的父親
To your dad.
我也從來沒和我爸喝過啤酒
I never had a beer with my dad, either.
能別插嘴嗎  我們喝得正歡呢
Do you mind? We're having a moment here.
真不敢相信佩妮嫁給了扎克
I can't believe Penny's married to Zack.
不知道她看上他哪一點
Wonder what she saw in that guy.
不知道
I don't know.
他可愛  高大  英俊
He's sweet, he's tall, handsome.
他有寬闊的肩膀  濃密的頭發
Broad shoulders, good hair.
不知道她看上萊納德哪一點
Wonder what she sees in Leonard.
外面情況如何
How's it going out there?
謝爾頓和你爸把酒言歡
Sheldon and your dad are bonding
完全無視我的存在
and completely ignoring me.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel.
他買了智能吸塵器后  無視了我一周
Sheldon ignored me for a week when he got that Roomba vacuum.
趁他不注意的時候  我踢了那玩意一腳
I kick it when he's not looking.
他們在做什么
What are they doing?
喝啤酒  看橄欖球比賽
They're drinking beer and watching football.
你就和他們一起唄
So why don't do that with them.
他們不要我
They don't want me.
什么意思
What do you mean?
謝爾頓開始訴說他的父親已經不在人世了
Well, Sheldon started talking about how his dad isn't alive anymore,
在他們碰杯時  我試圖告訴他們
and they were toasting, and I tried to tell them about
我父親拋棄我們時  我有多難過
how sad I was when my dad abandoned...
扎克到了
Zack's here!
攪拌肉汁
Stir the gravy.
對不起  我真的很想聽你有多難過
Sorry. I really want to hear how sad you are.
五到十分鐘后  我就會回來了
I'll be back in like five, ten minutes.
抱歉今天過節  她還讓你過來
Sorry she made you come over here on a holiday.
沒關系  反正我也沒安排
It's all right. I didn't have anything going on.
而且  佩妮說我們結婚了
Plus, Penny told me we're married,
感恩節就是要和家人一起
and Thanksgiving's a time to be with family.
非常好
Yeah, okay, great.
咱們速戰速決吧
Can we just get this over with?
好  在這里和這里簽名
Yeah, uh, you guys have to sign here and here.
星期一  我們會提出無效申請
On Monday, we'll file for the annulment,
這段婚姻就結束了
and this "Marriage" will be over.
好了
Okay.
我不確定我是否想簽這份文件
I don't know if I want to sign it.
你為什么不想簽
Why won't you sign it?
我只是覺得分手對孩子影響不好
I just think splitting up can be rough on kids.
我們沒有孩子
We don't have any kids.
你確定嗎  你也是
Are you sure? 'Cause you didn't know
今早才知道我們結婚了
we were married until this morning.
扎克  拜托
Okay, look, Zack, come on.
我們都知道那場婚禮不是真的
You know neither of us thought this was real.
主婚人是山寨貓王
I mean, we were married by an Elvis impersonator.
當然是山寨的了
Of course it was an impersonator.
真的貓王我們請不起好吧
We could never afford a real Elvis.
你居然嫁給他  不嫁給我
You married him instead of me?
真有眼光
Good call.
快簽字
Sign the papers.
慢著  算了
Hang on. You know what?
你一整天都是一副欠揍的態度
You have been a jerk about this all day.
你總是這樣  每次我犯了錯
You always do this-- whenever I mess up,
你就在旁邊數落我  讓我感覺更難受
you're right there to make me feel even worse about it.
才不是
That is not true.
我們本可以等到周一  再簽文件
Yeah, we could've waited till Monday, signed the papers,
這事就算過去了
this all would have been over.
是你把他叫過來的
You're the one who invited him here.
你又來了
Oh, there you go again--
又開始當著我的面數落我的錯誤
just another mistake you're throwing in my face.
這可不好  兄弟
Not cool, bro.
我開始覺得
I'm starting to think
我不想我老婆跟你這種人約會
you're not the kind of guy I want dating my wife.
好吧
Yeah, well,
她做你老婆的時間不會很久了
she's not gonna be your wife for long.
不是吧  你快死了嗎
Oh, no. Are you dying?
快了  快簽字吧
I'm about to. Sign the paper.
常言說得好  老婆開心
Know what they say: "Happy wife,
日子舒心
happy life."
開吃吧
Let's eat.
二  三  八  四  六
Two, three, eight, four, six.
再說就要吐了
That's all I can do without throwing up.
我可沒料到
That is not what I expected
你說打嗝說出π[餡餅]是這個意思
when you said you were gonna burp "Pie."
謝爾頓已經背到π的小數點后第20位
3. 14159 26535 89793 23846
剛有人說"餡餅"嗎
Did somebody say "Pie"?!
我不知道哪種更嚇人
I don't know what's scarier:
廁所小丑
the bathroom clowns
還是把小丑放進去的女人
or the woman that put them there.
我只知道  車上只能放下一個她
All I know is you can only fit one of her in a car.
那是從她身體里蹦出來的小丑
And there's the clown that came out of her.
我之前真的不想來
I really didn't want to come here,
但看來這次感恩節
but this is shaping up to be
是我多年以來過得最開心的一次
one of the best Thanksgivings I've had in a long time.
我也是
Me, too.
喂  華仔說你們一整天都在取笑他
Hey. Howie says you've been making fun of him all day!
現在你們兩個馬上道歉
Now, both of you apologize right now!
她個子好小啊
She's so tiny.
她生氣的樣子好好笑
It's funny when she's mad.
小伙子
All right, mister,
我想你應該向霍華德和伯納黛特道歉
I think you owe Howard and Bernadette an apology.
也許你是對的
Perhaps you're right.
我為我的行為道歉
I'm sorry for my behavior.
我攝入了酒精  導致我行為不當
I've had alcohol, and it's caused me to be inappropriate.
-沒事  -沒關系
- It's okay. - Don't worry about it.
謝謝
Thank you.
她是不是好賢惠
Ain't she great?
謝爾頓
Sheldon.
快去給老爺們兒拿啤酒吧
Now, how's about you get us a couple of beers?
再次感謝你下廚
Thanks again for cooking.
所有菜都超級好吃
Yeah, everything was delicious.
沒我最喜歡的兩個女生幫忙  我也做不到啊
Well, I couldn't have done it without my two favorite girls.
瑪莎·斯圖爾特和瑞秋·雷[廚藝天后]
Martha Stewart and Rachael Ray.
謝爾頓  我們出去
Hey, Sheldon, what do you say we go outside
玩下橄欖球如何[豬皮]
and throw around the old pigskin?
這家是猶太人
This is a Jewish house.
猶太人不吃豬肉
我想他們沒豬皮
I don't think they have pigskin.
剛有人說"豬皮"嗎
Did someone say pigskin!
親愛的  今天的事很抱歉
Hey, honey, I'm sorry about today.
我保證  下次結婚
And I promise, next time I get married,
絕對不會是鬧著玩
it won't be a joke.
一定是為了愛
It'll be for love.
或是錢
Or money.
我也抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
別這樣
Don't be.
都是我的錯
It's my fault.
我是個糟糕的老公
I was a terrible husband.
從未陪在老婆身邊
I was never around.
我知道我對你太嚴厲了
I know I'm hard on you,
但你不是世界上最差勁的女婿
but you're not the worst son-in-law in the world.
邁克  這是你對我說過的最貼心的話
Mike, that's the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
我喝醉了
Well, I'm drunk.
我剛剛吐在了很多小丑身上
I just vomited on a lot of clowns.